ajinomoto.com 2019-07-03

# Privacy Policy | Ajinomoto Group

Ajinomoto Co., Inc. ("Ajinomoto" or "we") strives to ensure appropriate treatment of your personal information, subject to the following privacy policy: 

  1. Ajinomoto complies with the Law concerning Protection of Personal Information and other applicable laws and regulations in handling your personal information. 
  2. When Ajinomoto collects personal information, we will make public a purpose statement that explains why personal information will be collected or notify you of such purpose. Should the purpose of use of your personal information you provided to us change, we will make public or notify you of the changed purpose. 
  3. Ajinomoto will not, without your prior consent, use your personal information beyond the extent necessary to accomplish the purpose of use set forth in the immediately preceding paragraph. 
  4. Ajinomoto already takes appropriate steps to ensure the safe management of your personal information to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, disclosure, loss and damage. 
  5. Ajinomoto will not provide third parties with your personal information without your prior consent except in cases where we delegate the handling of personal information to third parties to the extent necessary for the purpose of use or we provide personal information legally to a third party pursuant to laws, regulations or rules. 
  6. Ajinomoto appropriately responds to your request to disclose, correct, add or suspend the use of, the personal data you provide to us. For more information about this request, please contact the address or website through which you provided such personal information. 
  7. Ajinomoto strives to develop and improve the internal system designed to ensure appropriate treatment of personal information and to conduct ongoing personnel training programs for that purpose.
